Aysun SOYYİĞİT

Hello, I am Aysun. I am a senior student majoring in Labor Economics and Industrial Relations at Yalova University and Sociology at Anadolu University. My communication skills are at a high level and I have actively utilized this skill in my work experience. I am inclined towards working in the field of HR and I am always open to developing myself in this area.

I worked as an assistant at BHG ART for a year and gained important experience in how workplace processes are managed. Through this experience, I have developed skills in adapting to the workplace, time management, and teamwork.

I am proficient in programs such as Word and Excel and I can express myself comfortably in English.

In line with my career goals, I am constantly striving to develop myself in the industry and am open to gaining new experiences.

Education

2014-2018	Mimar Sinan Anatolian High School
2019 - 2023	Yalova University
	Bachelor's Degree in Labor Economics and Industrial Relations
2019 - 2023	Anadolu University
	Bachelor's Degree in Sociology

Experience

Project-based assistantship within BHG
Art, which organizes trainings on human resources by experts in the field.

Human resources analysis

Sense of responsibility

• Teamwork and team spirit

Dedicated work

2018 - 2021 Moulina Chocolat

Executive

Volunteering

2012 - 2023 Türkiye İzcilik Federasyonu

Support for the life-long education of young generations and service to the community.

Reference

Fatih Uzkan - BHG ART 0 555 978 8851



14.02.2000

Communication

0 535 308 12 37

aysunsoyyigit@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/aysun-soyyiğit

Skills

Communication	
Team Leadership	шш
Documentation	

Foreign languages

English Good

Russian Basic